<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carson Zhang</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Carson Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NBA Salary Estimation</title>
      <link>/post/nba-salary-estimation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nba-salary-estimation/</guid>
      <description>I use k-nearest neighbors regression to estimate fair salaries for NBA players based on the market for players of a similar caliber. I re-predict on the training set (gasp!), but use leave-one-out predictions to prevent severe overfitting. I argue that it is counterproductive to perform a test-train split when re-predicting on the training set because this will make predictions on the test set less accurate. I argue that using sophisticated ensemble learning methods is overkill, and less interpretable and useful than a simpler method such as k-nearest neighbors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I graduated with a BS in Statistics and Computer Science from the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. I like applying knowledge of those fields to organize, understand, and communicate information in engaging ways.
This will be a project portfolio, and a blog with data analyses, explanations of technical concepts, and opinions on life. Everything here is a living document - please let me know if you think I&amp;rsquo;m wrong.
I&amp;rsquo;m on the job market!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>